<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<templateItems template="/Templates/MediatedSculptureDetail.dwt" codeOutsideHTMLIsLocked="false">
   	<parameter name="name" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[Red Nimbus]]></parameter>
   	<parameter name="meta_description" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[The plaster torso might be a lost hero, warrior or philosopher, perhaps even a Greek bust of Plato? This plaster sculpture, which has literally lost its head, bears instead the porcelain doll’s head of a child, producing a marriage of mismatched scales and consciousness. ]]></parameter>
   	<parameter name="main_image_src" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[/media/images/red-nimbus-1.jpg]]></parameter>
	<parameter name="another_view_1" type="boolean" passthrough="false">true</parameter>
	<parameter name="another_view_1_src" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[/media/images/red-nimbus-2.jpg]]></parameter>
	<parameter name="another_view_2" type="boolean" passthrough="false">true</parameter>
	<parameter name="another_view_2_src" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[/media/images/red-nimbus-detail-3.jpg]]></parameter>
	<parameter name="video" type="boolean" passthrough="false">true</parameter>
	<parameter name="video_src" type="text" passthrough="false"><![CDATA[/media/videos/red-nimbus-640.f4v]]></parameter>
   	<item name="materials"><![CDATA[
					Plaster, porcelain, wood, LCD monitor, DVD player, audio speakers, video montage, speakers
					<br />
					74&Prime; &times; 32&Prime; &times; 23&Prime;
		]]></item>
	<item name="description"><![CDATA[
                    <p class="description">The plaster torso might be a lost hero, warrior or philosopher, perhaps even a Greek bust of Plato? This plaster sculpture, which has literally lost its head, bears instead the porcelain doll’s head of a child, producing a marriage of mismatched scales and consciousness. The top of the doll’s head originally designed to receive hair remains open, above which hovers a gold and red halo. The doll’s eyes shine with fluctuating light that projects from a digital screen buried in the head of this young hero-saint.</p>
                    <p class="description">This sacred figure oversees the proceedings, while at the same time its eyes are the subject of scrutiny. By peering through these open slots one can view a series filmic images of a martial Peking Opera mixed with a military documentary of the Hiroshima aftermath, Nazi Youth rallies, and adolescent counseling films.</p>
		]]></item>
   	<item name="head"><![CDATA[]]></item>
</templateItems>